

# **SAMI RAHMAN**

# **Full Stack Developer**

I am a versatile full-stack software developer, proficient in both frontend and back-end development, delivering comprehensive software solutions. As a full-stack web developer, I specialize in creating userfriendly websites, and as an IT consultant, I provide strategic technology guidance for efficient system optimization and data security.

#### **Contact Info**

+1 (236) 868-9379

jobs@srs404.com

www.linkedin.com/in/srs404
www.srs404.com
www.github.com/srs404

#### Education

## **Alexander College**

2023 - 2024

#### **Skills**

## **Full Stack Software Development**

JAVA, C++, PYTHON, .NET TripUp // Liqour Lounge

#### **Full Stack Web Development**

MEAN, MERN, JavaScript, PHP, MySQL, CSS3 TripUp // NSU ACM SC

### **System Server Administration**

Linux, Windows, Bash, Shell, User Role Management, Network Configuration TripUp // Personal Server

#### **Cyber Security Analysis**

BurpSuite, MetaSploit Framework, BeEF Framework, Social Engineering, ARP Poison, Custom Written Scripts and more. TripUp // NSU ACM SC // Liqour Lounge

# **Work Experience**

Senior IT Consultant // TripUp.io

2023 - Present

TripUp is a startup company started in 2022 focusing on building a one-stop solution for travel, where their users can find accommodation for short-term stays, tour packages, travel activities, tickets and many more.

Area Manager // Telus Communication

2022 - 2023

a leading Canadian telecommunications company that provides a wide range of telecommunications services, including wireless and wired internet, television, and home and business phone services.

IT Consultant // Travela

2022 - 2022 (1 Year Contract)

Travela is an on demand short term accommodation rental platform. Here, anyone can list their unused rooms/apartments, and guests can book these through our mobile apps.

Web Team Leader // NSU ACM Student Chapter

2019 - 2020

NSU ACM Student Chapter is one of the 680 chapters around the world and was the first student chapter of the Association for Computing Machineries in Bangladesh.